MD. AFJAL HOSEN

SEIP CERTIFIED DATA SCIENTIST

AWARDED PYTHON PROGRAMMER

Basically, I am a Programmer with 1 year of working and teaching experience at a BTEB certified polytechnic institute.

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Religion: Islam

Nationality: Bangladeshi Date of Birth: 02-02-2001 Marital Status: Unmarried

Gender: Male

Age: 22 Height: 5'5"

NID: 2865521724

Religion: Islam

PROFILE

Here, I am Md. Afjal Hosen. I am a Data Scientist with 1 year of analysis, freelancing, working and teaching experience. I like to work as a team leader.Because of my inter related skills, I can be the best option for you and your company.

EXPERIENCE

2022 - present

BACE Institute of Science & Technology (BIST)

INSTRUCTOR & DATA ANALYST (1 YEARS EXPERIENCE)

2021 - 2022

MERI Programmers

COURSE INSTRUCTOR FOR PYTHON & MACHINE LEARNING COURSE (15 MONTHS EXPERIENCE)

CONTACT



+880186-1803920



mdahmbsc01@gmail.com



https://github.com/AhMeraj



Bayderbazar, Sonargaon, Narayanganj

EDUCATION

Recent -

Hamdard University Bangladesh

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science & Engineering

CGPA: 3.40 out of 4 (2018-2022)

Previous -

Rofigul Islam School & College

HSC in Science - 3.42 out of 5 (2016-2018)

Northern University Laboratory School & College

SSC in Science - 4.61 out of 5

SKILLS

Data Science & Machine Learning

Data Analysis & Data Visualization

86%

MySQL & PowerBl

70%

Python/Django

C/Java/Python Programming

Data Structures & Algorithms

87%

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Recently earned a badge (Linkedin Skill Assessment badge) on my linkedin profile for Python Programming Language. Which badge means I am in the top 15% of 3.4M people who took this.
- Had nominated for NCPC 2020